嗨 我是 Becky Swaft
Hi, my name is Becky Swaft
我现在在密西根州立大学
And today I'm at Michigan State University
我将要问一些人
and I'm going to be asking several people
关于他们认为的健康饮食习惯的问题
questions about what they think about healthy eating styles.
我希望你可以注意
I want you to pay attention
并判断你同意还是不同意
and see what you think if you agree or disagree.
我要问的问题是
The question I'm gonna be asking is
你有哪些关于
what are some suggestions that you have
健康饮食的建议
for eating healthy
你有哪些关于健康饮食的建议
So what are some suggest for eating healthy?
我要说 每天一个苹果 医生远离我
I'll say an apple a day keeps the doctor away
我非常感激这句话
And I was really appreciate about it.
我要说的是
I would say
拒绝含糖饮料
avoid sugary drinks
我喜欢含糖饮料但要拒绝他们
I love it too but avoid them
我喜欢均衡的印时
I enjoy having a balanced diet
肉 水果 蔬菜等
the meat, the fruit, the vegetables.
对 如果你只吃一样东西
Yeah if you insis on one thing
就很有可能不健康
it is probabily not healthy.
你有哪些关于健康饮食的建议
What are some suggest for eating healthy?
我认为首先
Oh my think the first thing is
要喝大量的水
to drink lots of water.
每顿饭都要吃很多的
And to eat a lot of fruits and a lot vegetables
水果和蔬菜
with every meal
我比较喜欢做一件事
And one thing that I like to do
就是让我的盘子色彩缤纷
is to make my plate really colourful.
如果我有越多的
So there are more food I have
不同颜色的食物
with lots of different colors,
Hope to be property.
Hope to be property. That's it.
没了
That's it.
你有哪些关于健康饮食的建议
So what are some suggestions for eating healthy?
吃新鲜的食物
Eating fresh food
应季食物
and in season food.
而且我认为
And I think
减少半成品和外卖的食物
reduces the amount of processed and packaged food
他们常含有大量的防腐剂
which often has a lot of preservatives.
我觉得它们不健康
I thinks it isn't that are healthy.
所以要吃新鲜的 当地的 有机地食物
So eating fresh and local and organic
以确保你能从你所吃地食物中
you know make sure that you're getting the most nutrition
获得更多的营养
out of the food that you're eating.
你有哪些关于健康饮食的建议
What are some suggestions for eating healthy?
多吃水果和蔬菜
Eat lots of fruits and vegetables
尽量别吃糖
and try to avoid sweets.
你有哪些关于健康饮食的建议
What are some suggest for eating healthy?
我认为吃
I think it's important
大量的水果和蔬菜很重要
to eat a lot of fresh fruits and vegetables.
别吃半加工食物
And not eating process food
他们有很多糖分和盐分
that are hanging sugar and salt.
尽可能地保持新鲜
Probably trying to keep it as fresh as possible
在附近餐厅的时候 应该比你正常所需要的
You should probably have smaller portions than
更少份量的食物
you generally concerned at restaurants around here
还有
And
别吃太多垃圾食品
don't eat so much junk food.
我的建议是
Some suggestions would be
最小化各种糖分
to minimize the amount of sweets and sugar
以及甜点的摄入
and desserts that you eat.
确保你的每一餐都均衡的有
And make sure that if your meal is balanced with
大量的蔬菜和良好的蛋白质
plenty of vegetables and
来源来支持你日常代谢所需
a good source of protein to fill you up.
还有别吃含有太多碳水化合物的食品
And to not eat that has many carbohydrates.
你有哪些健康饮食的建议
What are some suggestions for eating healthy?
健康饮食
Eating healthy.
吃未加工过的蔬菜
Eating raw vegetables,
和尽量少加工的食物是最好的方法
less processed food is the best way to go.
hoo
Hookup with local farmers see s aco-oplike that
给人们提供了
providing people with
新鲜有机的蔬菜
fresh vegetables and organic vegetables.
你有哪些健康饮食的建议
What are some suggest eating healthy?
我认为自己做饭很重要
I think it's important to cook for yourself
比出去吃要好
rather than to eat out.
我认为
I think that
在你吃之前计划好你要吃什么
it's important to plan out what you're going to eat
也很重要
before you eat it.
And I think it's important
to watch your portion control.
你有哪些健康饮食的建议
What are some suggest for eating healthy?
首先我认为应该减少
First of all I think we should reduce the food
处理不充分的食物
which is least prepared
所以要尽可能多的多吃
so eat more and more raw vegetables
生水果和蔬菜
as much as possible.
你应该尽量少加工他们 用很少的油
You need to cook them less and with less oil
买当地的蔬菜
You should get local vegetables
当地产的食物会更好
local produce so much the better.
我尽量不买
I try not to buy
加工过的食物
processed food
所以我尝试
so I tried to cook from scratch
蔬菜 肉 面包
only by vegetables and meet and bread
我自己做
and I cook it myself.
别吃任何
Don't eat anything
你外婆不认为是食物的东西
that your grandmother wouldn't know is food.
我的健康饮食的建议是
Some suggestions for eating healthy
自己种蔬菜
are to grow your own food especially veggies
感觉会有更丰富的营养
are may feel like there more nutritious
因为他们直接来自
because they come straight from
你后院的地上
the ground in your backyard
你摘他们的时候他们仍然是新鲜的
when you pick up there really writing fresh
还有我觉得应该吃更多
And I also feel that you should load up on
好的谷物 蔬菜 水果
good grains and veggies and fruits
还有
And
在你吃饭的时候尽量在桌子上吃
when you eat I think you should eat at the table
这样你可以降低吃饭的速度
through that way you can slow down
更加小心地吃东西
and carefully eat your food.
嗨 又是我 Becky
Hi, it's me again, Becky.
我希望在你看了这么多人
I hope that you were able to understand
关于健康饮食地观点后
after hear a lot of different peoples opinions
你可以理解
on eating healthy.
但是现在我要去吃午饭了
But for me it's time for me to go to eat lunch.
我们在武汉见
So I will see you guys in Wuhan.
再见
Goodbye!